musicsubmit.com 2013-11-16

# MusicSUBMIT | Music Promotion and internet publicity for indie musicians

MusicSUBMIT LLC ("MusicSUBMIT") has created this web site to provide an online platform for musicians, music promoters and other music professionals.  

  To assist you in using our www. MusicSUBMIT.com web site (the "Web Site" or the "Site"), and to ensure a clear understanding of the relationship arising from your use of our Site, we have created a Privacy Policy and a set of 

. Our Privacy Policy explains how we protect and treat contact and other information you provide to us through the Site, and our Terms and Conditions of Use govern your use of our Site generally. Please read our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use carefully \- they impose legal obligations on you. By using or accessing our Site, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood these terms and agree to be legally bound by them. 

**Privacy Policy**

We respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") constitutes the agreement between you and MusicSUBMIT regarding your provision, and our collection and use, of contact and other information you may provide while using our Site. In this Privacy Policy, the words "you" and "your" refer to any person accessing the Site, and the words "we," "us," and "our" refer to MusicSUBMIT.  

  By using our Site, you consent to this Privacy Policy.  

  **1\. Overview**    
We have organized the elements of our Privacy Policy in sections. If after reading through the Privacy Policy you still have questions, please feel free to contact us by clicking on the following link: 

.   
**   
2\. The Types Of Information You Potentially May Provide**   
This Privacy Policy only applies to information you provide to us online while visiting or using our Site. It does not apply to information we have obtained offline or through other traditional means. Information you may provide in visiting or using our Site falls into two broad categories: personally identifiable information, and aggregate information. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, phone number, email address, or mailing address. "Aggregate Information" is information that does not identify you, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the web pages on our Site that users most frequent. Our Privacy Policy governs both categories of information, as detailed below.    
**   
2.1. Information That Identifies You: Personally Identifiable Information**   
We allow you to decide whether you wish to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information. Accordingly, we have structured our Web Site so that you may visit our Site, and review a range of information about bands, musicians other materials relating to the music industry, without revealing your identity or providing any Personally Identifying Information.  

  One of our goals in creating this Web Site, however, is to enable bands and musicians to post information about themselves and their music (for example, through a MusicSUBMIT Press Kit ("MPK™")), and to enable music promoters and other music professionals to access such postings and book appearances. Therefore, in order to post any such information and book appearances, and in order to access certain other materials or information from our Site, we ask that you register and provide us with contact and other information, as provided below.    
**   
2.1.1. Registration Information**   
To post information on our Site, and to obtain access to certain other materials or information from our Site, we ask that you become a registered user. Our registration forms will specify the information which you must provide in order to enjoy the particular feature, and the information which you may, at your option, choose to provide or withhold. Our obligations concerning, and permitted uses of, any Personally Identifiable Information that you provide during the registration process are set out below.  

  As indicated above, you may use our Site without registering or submitting any information to us. In that case, the only information we collect from your visit will be Aggregate Information that does not identify you in any way. Our obligations concerning, and permitted uses of, Aggregate Information are also set out below.    
**   
2.1.2. Surveys and Questionnaires **   
If you choose to participate in surveys or questionnaires which from time to time we may post on the Site, we may ask that, in addition to providing your responses, you also provide contact and other Personally Identifiable Information. If we link, or combine in any way your responses with your Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat the combined information as Personally Identifiable Information under our Privacy Policy, as provided below. If we separate your responses from, and they are independent of any Personally Identifiable Information, such that a third party reviewing your responses would be unable to link the responses to you or your practice, the responses will be treated as Aggregate Information under our Privacy Policy, again as provided below.    
**   
2.1.3. Email And Other Direct Communications**   
From time to time, you may wish to provide us with comments and feedback concerning our Site generally. By communicating with us for these purposes, you may provide us with your email address and other Personally Identifiable Information. We will handle such information that you provide in this manner in accordance with our Privacy Policy for Personally Identifiable Information, set out below.    
**   
2.2. Information That Does Not Identify You: Aggregate Information**   
When you browse our Site, the choices you make may provide information concerning your interests and concerning the appeal and efficacy of associated Site features. For example, if you spend time browsing information on events taking place in Georgia and Florida, this suggests that you may have an interest in events in the Southeast generally. If a number of visitors spend time browsing information on events taking place in Georgia and Florida, this may suggest that we have designed this portion of our Site effectively.  

  Information concerning our visitors' activities at the Site \- which pages they visit, and how long they view these pages, for example - is Aggregate Information. This information does not identify a particular user, but does provide potentially useful data concerning our users' preferences and the efficacy and interest of our Site's features. The manner in which we collect Aggregate Information is set out below. 

  **2.2.1. Cookies**    
We collect Aggregate Information about your use of our Site through cookies and similar Internet technologies. "Cookies" are small text files that a web site can use to recognize repeat users, to facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site, and to compile aggregate data to improve the site and focus advertising. Cookies work as follows: a web site will send a cookie to your browser that uniquely associates your computer with information stored at the site. Your browser places the cookie in its cookies file. When you next access that site on your computer, the site recognizes the cookie, makes the stored information available, and adds new information based on the present visit.  

  Our cookies do not collect or retain your name or other Personally Identifying Information. In addition, no third parties are permitted to use cookies created at our Site for their own purposes.  

  We treat all information collected through cookies and similar Internet technologies as Aggregate Information; our obligations concerning, and permitted uses of, Aggregate Information are set out below.  

  **2.2.2. Disabling Cookies**    
You may choose not to allow us to collect information through cookies. If you wish, you can set your browser software to reject cookies, and most browsers provide instructions for disabling the cookies feature in their "Help" section. Because cookies can be used to provide certain functionality, if you disable your browser's cookies feature, certain elements of our Site may be unavailable to you.  

  **2.2.3. IP Addresses**    
A so-called "Internet Protocol" (IP) address is associated with your computer's connection to the Internet. We use your computer's IP address to maintain contact with you as you navigate through our Site. We also may use your computer's IP address to provide you with personalized content. Similar to cookies, your computer's IP address by itself does not identify you personally. We treat IP addresses, therefore, as Aggregate Information, as provided below. If your IP address is combined by us with any Personally Identifiable Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personally Identifiable Information, as set out below. 

  **2.2.4. Advertisers' Collection Of Information**    
With Internet technology, it is possible for advertisers, as well as site hosts, to collect information through the use of cookies and other technologies, such as so-called "clear GIF" files. We have no control over, and cannot necessarily protect against, the practices or policies of advertisers or other web site hosts using such technologies.    
**   
3\. How We Use The Information You Provide **   
The following section describes how we use the information you provide, and details the specific obligations we undertake to preserve your privacy.  

  **3.1. Use of Contact Information**    
We use Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us on our Site to post your MPK™ and other submissions, and for other purposes specific to our Site. In connection with postings you may request we make on the Site, users of our Site shall have access to such information - which may include personal information about you. For example, your name, address, telephone number and/or email address may be included in your MPK™ listing or other submissions you request we post for contact purposes.  

  From time to time, we also may use Personally Identifiable Information you give to us to provide you with information concerning newsletters, updates, and other materials related to the purposes of our Site. We also will use this information to respond to questions and comments from you, and to inform you of changes to our Privacy Policy or Terms and Conditions of Use. You are free at any time to opt-out of receiving email and other information we may send to you by following the directions set out below.    
**   
3.2. We Use Aggregate Information Only In Ways That Do Not Identify You**   
To measure our visitors' interest in and use of various areas of our Site, and for other purposes set out below, we collect Aggregate Information -- which is information that does not identify you. Aggregate Information obtained through cookies, for example, allows us to monitor how many users are visiting our Site, and what areas of the Site present the most interest to our users. We are able then to use this information to improve the functionality and interest of Site. We also use Aggregate Information to prepare statistical and other summary analyses of our users' behavior and characteristics. 

We may share Aggregate Information, and reports based on this Information, with third parties unrelated to the Site. Rest assured, however, that no such Aggregate Information that we provide to third parties will allow anyone to identify you, or determine anything personal about you. For example, we might report to unrelated third parties (a) the number of users of our Site; (b) the materials our users review while at our Site; or (c) the fact that "45% of our users live on the East Coast." We may charge third parties for this information, and we may or may not limit the third parties' use of this information. We do not allow third parties to attempt to make Aggregate Information personally identifiable by, for example, seeking to combine it with other information. 

  **3.3. Any Information Linked With Your Personal Information Is Treated As "Personally Identifiable Information"**    
To advance the goals of our Site, we may link (a) the Personally Identifiable Information you have provided; with (b) Aggregate Information concerning (for example) your interests and preferences, as collected through our cookies. Linking this information will allow us to create information packages and services that are better tailored to your interests and preferences. Among other effects, linking this information may allow us generally to improve and focus our Site. If we combine or link any information with your Personally Identifiable Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, please be aware that in such instances, personal information about you may be made generally available on the Site in connection with postings you may request we make on the Site, as set forth above.  

  **4\. How We Safeguard Information We Collect**    
We have put in place security systems designed to prevent unauthorized disclosure of information you provide to us. These systems are structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing this information. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, however, we cannot provide, and disclaim, assurance that the information you provide us will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access.    
**   
5\. How To Obtain Access to Information You Have Provided, And How To Remove Your Information From Our Database**   
We allow you at any time to update, correct, or delete Personally Identifiable Information you have provided us. After submitting your registration information, you can view and modify this information within the "Edit Profile" page of the Site. 

  If you request, we will remove your name and other Personally Identifiable Information from our databases. Please understand, however, that it may be impossible to remove this information completely, due to backups and records of deletions. If you wish to remove your name and other Personally Identifiable Information from our database, please contact us. 

  Because Aggregate Information does not personally identify our users, we do not provide our users with access to Aggregate Information, and users may not update, revise, or delete any Aggregate Information.  

  **6\. Additional General Provisions**

  **6.1. Privacy Protection for Children**    
Our Site is not directed at children, and we will not accept or request personal information from individuals we know to be under 13. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided us with Personally Identifiable Information, we will delete this information from our databases, in accordance with our deletion policy, set out above. 

  **6.2. Participation in Online Discussions**    
If we include a "chat" or "forum" feature to the Site, you may decide to participate in an online discussion. Please keep in mind that any information you provide while participating in an online chat or forum will be available to all participants. These participants, and their transferees, may use Personally Identifiable Information and other information you disclose in this manner, to contact you and for other purposes. Accordingly, if we choose to provide such features at the Site, we ask that you participate prudently, as this Privacy Policy will not cover the information you disclose in online discussions at our Site.  

  **6.3. Links To Other Web Sites**    
To give you access to other information relating to the music industry, from time to time we may include on the Web Site certain links to other sites. We provide these links as a convenience, and we do not endorse the content or services offered by, or the privacy policies in place at, these other sites.  

  Our Privacy Policy covers only information we collect at the Site, and other sites to which we link may have privacy policies that differ considerably from our Privacy Policy. We have structured our Site to make it reasonably clear when you leave our Web Site and enter another web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of each site you visit through our links to ensure you are comfortable with these policies. We are not responsible for the conduct or policies of these third parties.    
**   
6.4. Court Orders, Subpoenas, And Other Required Disclosures**   
There are two exceptions to our Privacy Policy. First, we may disclose Personally Identifiable Information as may be required in legal proceedings, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or administrative order compelling disclosure. Second, in cases involving a threat of imminent harm to you or others, we may release such information to prevent or mitigate the threat. In any such case, we will seek to limit the scope of disclosure, and will disclose only such information as is reasonably required to fulfill the purpose of the disclosure.  

  **6.5. Changes in Our Privacy Policy**    
From time to time we may revise our Privacy Policy. We will post these changes here, in our Privacy Policy. Your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as changed.  

  **6.6. Relationship to Term of Use**    
In addition to this Privacy Policy, your use of our Site is also subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use (our "Terms of Use"). The provisions of our Terms of Use are incorporated herein, including, without limitation, Sections 12 (Choice of Law and Jurisdiction), 14 (Assignment), 17 (Severability), 18 (Survival) and 19 (Complete Agreement).  

  **7\. Your Consent**    
By using our Web Site, you consent to our collection and use of information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with some, or all of the terms of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from becoming a registered user, or from visiting our Site.  

  **8\. Contact Us**    
You may contact us, for any reason, by e-mail as follows:  

**You may contact us by mail as follows:**    
MusicSUBMIT LLC   
26 W. 90th St., Suite 2   
NY, NY 10024
